<!--
  ByteSip plugin descriptor.
  Registers:
    - A notification group used for all break reminders.
    - An application service that owns the scheduler.
    - A post-startup activity that boots the scheduler when a project opens.
-->
<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.bytesip</id>
    <name>ByteSip</name>
    <vendor email="abidinberkay@gmail.com" url="https://github.com/berkaysimsek">Berkay Simsek</vendor>

    <description><![CDATA[
        <h2>ByteSip — Healthy Coding Reminders for Developers</h2>

        <p>Tired of coding for hours without a break? <b>ByteSip</b> is your friendly wellness companion that lives inside your IDE. It quietly reminds you to take care of yourself with witty, non-intrusive balloon notifications — so you can keep shipping code without sacrificing your health.</p>

        <h3>Features</h3>
        <ul>
          <li><b>Water reminders</b> — every 25 minutes, because your kidneys deserve better than coffee.</li>
          <li><b>Eye-rest reminders</b> — every 50 minutes, following the 20-20-20 rule for healthier eyes.</li>
          <li><b>Movement reminders</b> — every 90 minutes, so your spine doesn't file a critical bug report.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>Why ByteSip?</h3>
        <ul>
          <li>🎈 <b>Non-blocking notifications</b> — appears as a balloon at the bottom of your IDE, never interrupts your flow.</li>
          <li>😄 <b>Funny, motivating messages</b> — randomly picked from a curated pool to keep things fresh.</li>
          <li>⏸️ <b>Snooze or Done actions</b> — quickly dismiss or postpone with a single click.</li>
          <li>⚙️ <b>Zero configuration</b> — install it and it just works. No setup required.</li>
          <li>🪶 <b>Lightweight</b> — minimal resource usage, runs silently in the background.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3>How It Works</h3>
        <p>ByteSip automatically starts when you open a project. It runs three independent timers — one for each reminder type — and displays a balloon notification at the bottom-right of your IDE when it's time for a break. Each notification includes a quick "Done" or "Snooze" action so you stay in control.</p>

        <p><b>Code happy. Stay hydrated. Take breaks. Ship better code.</b></p>
    ]]></description>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
        <h3>1.0.0 — Initial Release</h3>
        <ul>
          <li>Water, eye-rest, and movement reminders with fixed intervals.</li>
          <li>Randomized funny messages for each reminder type.</li>
          <li>Done and Snooze actions on every notification.</li>
          <li>Non-blocking balloon notifications.</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></change-notes>

    <!-- Required platform module. -->
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <!-- Single balloon notification group used by all break reminders. -->
        <notificationGroup id="ByteSip"
                           displayType="BALLOON"
                           isLogByDefault="false"/>

        <!-- Application-level service owning the shared scheduler. -->
        <applicationService serviceImplementation="com.bytesip.BreakScheduler"/>

        <!-- Run once when a project finishes loading. Boots the scheduler. -->
        <postStartupActivity implementation="com.bytesip.ByteSipStartupActivity"/>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
